Home! Home?
Home!
Home? Home!
Could be around any corner.
♪ Tra-la-la-la! Tra-la-la-la! ♪
♪ Chop the wood to light the fire ♪
Hey, captain, do you hear that singing?
♪ Tra-la-la-la! Tra-la-la-la! ♪
Graawr
Not you, skipper.
I'm talking to the captain.
♪ Tis it much that I require! ♪
Captain Wirt, do
you know who's singing?
I don't know much
of anything anymore.
♪ When the fog of life surrounds you, ♪
Oh.
Did you know that dinosaurs had big ears,
♪ when you feel you've lost your way! ♪
but everyone forgot 'cause dinosaur ears don't have bones?
♪ Come with me and join the forest, ♪
No. I... I didn't know that, Greg.
♪ Come with me and join the play! ♪
That's 'cause it's not true.
It's a rock fact!
♪ Tra-la-la-la! Tra-la-la-la! ♪
The beast.
It must be the beast out there.
♪ Youth is such a fragile thing. ♪
The obsidian cricket of our inevitable twilight
♪ Tra-la-la-la! Tra-la-la-la! ♪
singing our requiem.
♪ A fragile thing is what it is. ♪
Hmm. Yeah!
Must be a really fat cricket.
Look! We've reached land!
Feel the dirt!
Ahh. Smell that tree.
We must be almost there.
Greg?
Yes, Wirt?
Can we please stop pretending we're gonna get home?
Huh?
Can we admit we're lost for good?
This fog is deeper than we can ever understand?
We are but wayward leaves,
scattered to the air
by an indifferent wind?
Can we just admit we're never gonna get back home, Greg?
Can we do that?
Wirt, you can do anything if you set your mind to it.
That's what the old people say.
Well, then let's do that.
Yes, sir, captain!
Greg!
You need to stop acting ridiculous all the time.
Huh?
Look, do you even know why we got lost in the first place?
It's 'cause you were goofing around
and getting into trouble like you always do.
Really? It was all my fault?
Yeah, so...
it's not my job to get us home, okay?
I'm done.
Are you saying I should be the leader?
I don't care what you do.
But if I'm the leader...
what are you gonna be?
I'll be asleep.
Wow. Well...
then I better take a nap, too.
I need to dream up a good way of leading us home.
Thanks for trusting me, Wirt.
Don't worry.
I won't let you down.
I'll be a good leader.
Good night.
Star, oh, star, up in the sky,
guide my dreams with light that shines.
Help me know just what to do
to get Wirt home and also me, too.
And if you don't, I don't care.
I'll pull down your underwear.
♪ Forward, cherubs ♪
♪ hear the song ♪
♪ a child's wishes ♪
♪ call us on ♪
♪ Descend! Descend! ♪
Psst! Hey!
Huh? Whoa!
♪ The dreams our winged ♪
♪ wind hath made ♪
♪ for only beneath ♪
♪ the veil ♪
Whoa.
♪ Of sleep ♪
WhooOooa!
Whoa!
Whooooaa!
Wow!
Hey, Greg!
- Hello!
- Welcome!
- Nice to see you!
- Hello!
Come on in!
Hey, everybody!
Welcome to Cloud City!
Thank you! Thank you!
My name's Greg.
What are yours?
♪ We're the Cloud City ♪
♪ Reception Commitee! ♪
♪ And we are here to welcome thee ♪
Oh, wow, neat.
♪ And we're the Cloud City ♪
♪ Auxiliary Reception Committee ♪
♪ and we are also here
to welcome thee ♪
Thank you.
♪ And we're the hippopotamus,
giraffe, and monkey ♪
♪ and we are committee no. 3 ♪
Okay. Are there more?
Well, that's enough.
So, what brings you to Cloud City?
Well, I'm supposed to be a leader,
but I don't know how.
Why don't you lead our band in a song?
Okay.
♪ Everything is nice
and fine all the time ♪
♪ the softest clouds and rainbow skies ♪
♪ ain't gonna lie ♪
♪ we always have the most
spectacular time together ♪
♪ everyone is sittin' pretty
on top of the weather ♪
♪ lasso a cloud and
make the flowers grow ♪
♪ tie them in a bow to throw
at the end of the show ♪
♪ our songs are filled with love ♪
♪ the sweetest love ♪
♪ and we can send them down to you ♪
♪ with a little shove ♪
♪ so hitch a ride into the sky ♪
♪ and join our band ♪
♪ bring harps and lutes, kazoos,
trombones and flutes ♪
♪ or just your pots and pans ♪
♪ we can write a little jig
out of the mighty blue ♪
♪ and we will be here just for you- ♪
Hehe...
Bonk.
Oh, nooooo!
The North wind is loose!
♪ Oh, yeah, the ol' North wind ♪
♪ starts to howl ♪
♪ puffs up and furrows his brow ♪
♪ now, now ♪
♪ you better take cover ♪
♪ lock up those doors ♪
♪ and close the shutters ♪
♪ I say, the ol' North wind ♪
♪ yes, he is ♪
♪ he's gonna fight ♪
♪ he's gonna spin ♪
♪ he's gonna pull back ♪
♪ and blow a little more ♪
♪ until you can't tell
what you came here for ♪
♪ oh, yeah The ol' North wind♪
Fire!
♪ Yes, indeed ♪
♪ he's gonna breathe and breathe ♪
♪ he's gonna blow ♪
♪ blow till you can't feel no more ♪
Wirt? Greg?
Is anyone out there?
Ah!
Hey, North wind!
Pbht!
Errh, I don't like that one bit.
That makes me mad!
Oh, no!
Hee hee hee hee!
Huh?
Why, hello, Gregory.
Hello.
I am the Queen of the Clouds.
Thank you for saving my city.
You're welcome.
I shall grant you one wish.
What do you wish for most of all?
Well, I'm supposed to be the leader, but I don't know how to get home.
Do you know?
Of course.
If you wish, I can gcertainly send you home.
Great! Let's go get Wirt.
I'm sorry, Gregory,
but Wirt cannot go with you.
He is too lost.
Huh!
But...
anything is possible if you set your mind to it, right?
See how the edelwood grows around him?
The beast has claimed him already.
Oh, I should have
been leading better.
I was goofing off again, like always,
and now you're stuck here.
Isn't there anything I can do?
I'm sorry, Gregory.
Wirt's fate lies solely in the beast's hands now.
Then I know what to wish for.
Are you sure?
Then it shall be done.
Hey. Hey, Wirt?
Shh! I'm trying to sleep!
Okay. You sleep.
I'm sorry I got us lost, Wirt.
Will you take care of Ronald for me?
Okay. I have to go now.
Goodbye, Wirt.
Yes. Come, Gregory.
There is much to be done.
and then you'll show us the way home, right?
Of course.
We made a promise, didn't we?
Greg. Greg?
Greg? Greg?!
Where did he go?
♪ Tra-la-la-la! Tra-la-la-la! ♪
No. No, no, no, no!
Greg?!
♪ Chop the wood to light the fire ♪
♪ Tra-la-la-la! Tra-la-la-la! ♪
What the heck?
♪ Tis it much that I require! ♪
Greg?!
Greg... What did I do?
Greg! Greg!
♪ when you feel you've lost your way! ♪
♪ Come with me and join the forest, ♪
Huh? Greg!
♪ Come with me and join the play! ♪
♪ Tra-la-la-la! Tra-la-la-la! ♪
Oh! You got him!
Pull! Pull!
Is he alive?
- Wirt!
- Wirt? Wirt!
Gr...eg...?
Wirt, are you okay?
Wirt!
Gr...eg? I-I-I...
Where's Greg, Wirt?
Beatrice?
Wirt? Wirt!